October 7, 2007.
Four days till we deploy.
Grace knows I would do
anything to get back to her.
Anything.
Today I wrote her a letter.
Good afternoon, sir. I have the briefing
papers from the colonel's office.
Put them on the desk.
Thank you, Corporal.
Major. Hey.
Hope you don't have to deliver it.
Copy that.
- Be safe out there, Sam.
- Thanks, sir.
- See you when you get back.
- All right.
How's this?
Warm.
- Hello.
- Dad!
Hey! Hey, baby.
- Hi, Daddy.
- How you doing?
- How was school?
- Great.
They gave me Noodles the
dog. She's in my room.
Izzie?
Hey.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
What's wrong, honey?
You're leaving again.
Come give your daddy a hug.
No.
Come on. Give me a kiss, honey.
Just go.
- Two kisses?
- No.
Three kisses?
I wanna read my book.
You wanna read your book?
Oh, yeah?
I see a smile coming. There it is! There
it is! Now, you're getting 100 kisses!
- Behind you! Right behind you!
- What? What? What? Who? Who?
Wait a second! Two against
one. That is no fair!
Daddy, put me down!
Girls.
- Come on. Daddy's gotta go.
- Okay.
Please stay. Please let him stay.
- Yeah. Can't you stay?
- It's my brother.
He doesn't deserve you.
Go rob another bank, Tommy!
Bring that money back to me, brother!
See you later.
What happened to my little brother?
No fucking way.
You ever think of
apologizing to that woman?
It's green.
I got it.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know. I'm just gonna cash
this check, and then who knows.
- I'll see you later?
- Yeah, all right. All right.
- Don't rob the place.
- Yeah. Get the fuck out of here.
No hot water in this place?
Fucking hot water is missing.
I'm sorry.
How do you stand this kitchen?
He didn't expect to be
deploying again so soon.
Yeah. Well, are you
ripping your hair out?
What are you gonna do?
They call, you answer.
- Don't tell her. Oh, no.
- Yes!
- I won.
- She got you, Granddad.
You're raising a real
hustler here, Grace.
I know.
My birthday's this spring.
It is, isn't it? What is it,
March 10th, something like that?
- Hi.
- Are you Isabelle?
- No, I'm Maggie.
Isabelle's big.
I'm Tommy.
Mom doesn't like you.
Maggie!
What? That's what you said to Dad.
These are for your mom.
Mom, they're for you.
Thank you.
Come in.
- Hey. Hi, sweetie.
- Hey.
Come here.
Hi.
You made it.
Yeah.
- Son.
- Sir.
- What? Hi.
- Hi.
Bless us, O Lord, in these thy
gifts which we are about to receive
from thy bounty through
Christ, our Lord. Amen.
- Amen.
And this is a very special meal for us
because we are welcoming one son home,
and we're sending another one off.
And we ask you, Lord, to keep him safe
and bring him back really soon. Right?
- Yeah.
- Amen.
Here. You can do it.
- You wanna try?
- Thank you, Mom.
- Here, let me.
- Thanks, Mama.
Carrots are delicious.
- Why aren't you eating your peas?
- I hate peas.
I do, too.
Honey, eat your peas.
Okay, Dad.
I like peas.
So do I.
- When are you leaving?
- Tuesday.
You love it over there, huh?
It's my job.
They only shoot the bad guys.
Who are the bad guys?
The ones with the beards.
Your brother's a hero.
He's serving his country, and
don't you ever forget that.
Will you be here for my birthday?
You know I will, sweetie.
Sarah Miller's dad wasn't
there for her birthday.
- Isabelle.
- It's true.
She had to bring him a cake in prison.
It's not just military families.
There's a lot of folks
under pressure these days.
They got problems in all walks of life.
Every family's got their
own set of problems.
They sure do.
What is that supposed to mean?
Every family has their
own set of problems.
You sound like a damn parrot.
Like a what?
Why don't you try mimicking
your brother for a change?
Dad.
This food is great, Elsie. Thank you.
Compared to what?
Other food.
Prison food?
Tommy!
Excuse me.
It's okay, honey.
- No. No.
- It's his first night out.
He comes waltzing in here with
no regard for anybody else.
Doesn't even bother to apologize...
Stay out of trouble.
All right.
You be safe over there. All right?
This thing's not coming off.
- Try more soap.
- Yeah.
Almost got it.
There we go.
- Don't lose that.
- I'll do my best.
Okay.
- Take a lot of pictures when I'm gone.
- I always do.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Sam?
Take me with you.
Sure.
How about I go and
you stay with the kids?
Okay.
Don't go.
October 12, 2007.
Back in Afghanistan with my men.
Weird. It almost feels like home.
Hi, Cassie. Joe Jr. is so big.
What's the distance to the LZ?
We're three minutes out.
Clear to detach to the LZ.
Roger that.
Clear to engage. Weapons hot.
Target took cover in the valley.
Little bastards...
Who is it?
It's Captain Sanderson
and Chaplain Davis.
Hi.
- Hi. Is your mother home?
- Yeah.
Where is she?
In the bath.
Would you call her for us, please?
What's wrong?
Izzie.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Come in.
You've reached Captain Sam
Cahill. Please leave a message.
Grace.
Sorry. I didn't mean to wake you.
I was just dropping off the car.
Sam told me I could borrow
it whenever I wanted, so...
The taillight's a little
busted. Some asshole...
Look, you know...
Just say it, you know
what I mean? All right.
He told me I could borrow the
car whenever I wanted, Grace.
You look at me with
this pissed-off look.
Sam's dead.
They crashed.
- What are you talking about?
- He's dead, Tommy.
Come in, come in.
I don't wanna fucking come in.
I just came here to drop off...
- Why didn't you call me?
- I've been trying to call you all night.
- Why didn't anybody call me?
- We've all been trying, Tommy.
Okay.
- Why'd you let him go over there, Grace?
- Tommy.
For what now, huh?
Tommy, come inside.
I just had to sit down for a second.
He's with your mama
now. They're together.
Drink?
No.
Girls? You ready?
Yeah, in about just one minute.
- Why'd you take your dress off?
- I hate it.
We're going to put it
on, okay? We have to go.
I don't want to.
I don't want to wear
mine either. It's itchy.
Okay, come here. Okay.
Come here.
- Okay.
- Is Dad really dead like your mom and dad?
- I'm sorry.
- I appreciate it.
- I'm so sorry, dear.
- Thanks for coming.
Sir, your son's the best
damn Marine I ever commanded.
I appreciate it.
- Come on, girls.
- Coming, Grandpa.
- Get in the car.
- Come on, Maggie.
- Elsie, I'm sorry for your loss.
- I'll watch them.
Okay.
Grace, Sam wrote this for you before he left.
He never wanted me to have to deliver it.
I don't believe it, John.
I can't feel it.
Shouldn't I be able to feel it?
It's hard to accept. He was
a good friend, a good Marine.
- Why don't you let me drive?
- What are you talking about?
- Come on, girls.
- Coming.
Hey, why don't you
give me the keys, Dad?
What makes you so
responsible all of a sudden?
Let Tommy drive.
"Let Tommy drive."
Look, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you get a
job and earn some money,
buy yourself a car,
and then you can drive it
wherever the hell you want.
Give me the keys.
Did you hear those Marines in there
today talking about your brother?
Did you?
Who is gonna stand up and
testify for you once you're dead?
Yeah, it's my fault Sam's dead.
Right? That's what you think.
It's got nothing to do with you. Right?
- What are you saying to me?
- Hank.
Forget it.
You never had any guts.
And you did.
That's why you screamed
at Mom every fucking night.
That's why you drove us drunk,
huh? "Hang in there, Marines."
- Don't. Come on.
- Why you put all that shit in his head.
- You could never fill his shoes.
- I know that.
- Never could make me proud.
- For Lord's sake.
That is a sin.
- Stop it. Give me the keys.
- Here you go. I'm walking.
This is a nightmare.
What's going on?
What are they gonna do with us?
That yours?
Yeah.
That your wife?
Cassie, yeah.
No, she's not.
You don't have a wife.
You don't have a family.
I'm the only person you know.
It's Private Willis and Captain
Cahill. You know nothing else.
Yes, sir.
- Hello?
- Grace.
Tommy?
- Hi. I know it's like 1:00 in the morning.
- Yeah. It's 3:00.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
Okay. I had...
I had a couple of
drinks and, apparently,
they're the most expensive
drinks in the world. And...
Now I owe, like, $47.
I was gonna just walk out, but then
this guy says that he was
gonna nick me on a disorderly.
And then I'd lose my parole, so...
Which bar?
Your nose is like the lunar eclipse.
- Come on, let me touch it. Let me just...
- Get your hands off me, Tommy.
- Let me just touch it for a sec.
- Tommy, I'm sick of you. I'm sick of you.
Don't get so upset with me.
- All right. Go ahead.
- Thanks.
See. Nothing to it. Right?
- Big deal.
- That thing's huge, man.
- Hi.
- Great.
- How much does he owe you?
- $47 and two broken glasses.
- Well, how about we say...
- Ready?
- Come on, Cyrano.
- Get your hands off the bar.
- Don't try to ignore it. That thing's huge.
- How about we say $50. Okay?
- I don't care about the money...
- That thing's huge.
...just get him out of here. I'm
gonna call the cops. I'm done.
Tommy, I have two little girls sleeping
in a parking lot at 3:00 in the morning.
You think you're funny?
Go home.
Oh, God.
- My head's spinning.
- Be careful.
- I don't think I should be carrying a child.
- Just put her in her bed, okay?
Oh, my God.
- Uncle Tommy.
- Oh, my God.
Uncle Tommy, wake up.
Can you stop that?
I'm making pancakes for Mom.
I can't stop. My sister said.
Stop it.
No.
What are you doing here?
You want me to whisk in your face, too?
This is not your house, and
you're not the boss of me.
Come on.
We're making pancakes for
Mom, so she won't be sad.
- Our dad's dead.
- He knows. He's his brother.
I know that.
No drinking out of
the carton! It's gross!
Shut up. You're gross.
- No!
- You want a pancake?
No, I don't like pancakes.
- Our pancakes are the best.
- Eat your own crap, all right?
Mom! You're supposed to be upstairs.
- What are you doing awake?
- It's a surprise!
I am surprised. Thank you.
The nicest little girls in the world.
Who's that?
- Grandpa!
- Hey, babies.
- Hi!
- What have you got in your hair?
- Pancake batter.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hey, let's go watch TV.
- Come on, girls.
- I'll get the syrup.
- What a mess.
- Bye, Tommy.
- We'll clean this up later.
Morning.
Pancakes, huh?
Yeah, actually there's one
on the floor if you want it.
- What are they doing in here?
- They were making pancakes.
Look...
- I was a little stupid the other day.
- Yeah, hey.
- I was okay to drive, though.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know. I know.
I know Sam was always smarter than me.
Well, I don't know about smarter.
He was a damn good athlete.
Remember that game against Easton?
Cool as ice.
You had some talent,
too, you know. I mean...
You just quit all the time.
Now, that was the difference
between you and him.
Sam had no quit in him.
I'd cut my throat to
bring him back, Dad.
God damn it.
I don't know how she lives
with this kitchen the way it is.
Private, come here. Fucking help me.
I can't see anything.
They're looking for us.
All right.
- Should we try again?
- Not right now.
Come on, man. Just put
it where you got it.
Grace. Hey.
You remember, A.J., Owen.
Sweeney... I don't
remember your first name.
There's a reason for that.
- It's nice to meet you, Grace.
- You, too.
What's going on?
We're just fixing up
the kitchen for you.
Tommy.
Were you ever going to run this by me?
- Can you believe it? She's gorgeous.
- It's my house.
- Somebody's all growed up.
- It's not funny.
What the hell is wrong
with you guys? She's been...
You have to run this by me.
I was...
- Can I get you guys coffee, something?
- No, thanks.
- Maybe a beer.
- I would like a beer, too.
Don't tell them anything.
Don't you tell them anything, Private.
They're not asking me anything.
They're just starving us.
Stay calm, Private.
- Be present.
- I am fucking present.
I'm fucking present. I've been present
in this shithole for two fucking months.
What the fuck did you save me
for? Why did you come after me?
I should've drowned in that lake.
We'd both be better off dead.
What day is it?
Saturday.
What time is it?
About noon.
You remember what I told you.
No information. You give them nothing.
You give them nothing, Private.
Yeah.
- Where are they taking us?
- Don't speak. Don't speak!
- Are they gonna cut our heads off?
- Not another fucking word!
Welcome.
I used the satellite
phone to call my wife.
She's pregnant.
I jeopardized your
location and your mission.
We have the same blood.
Syed is my nephew.
Fuck them.
This is our country.
You should not be here.
Tell this message to America.
You say it,
or I'll force you to say it.
The girls are back.
It's a good thing downstairs.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks, Elsie.
Okay.
- Who is painting the kitchen?
- I am.
Get that spot right there.
You know, your dad was a great
football player in high school.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He was small, but he
was a great quarterback.
Me and A.J. and Owen used to go to
the games just to watch him play.
Did you ever have a
chance to see him play?
No.
- Izzie, you're so tall.
- Thanks.
- Good job, Mag.
- Thanks, Mom.
Do they need to do their
homework or something?
No. She's having fun.
Get these real good.
Shit the bed!
- What are you doing?
- Painting.
These are brand new pants.
- Hey, man...
- I'm sorry.
Chill out, man. She said she was sorry.
It's okay, Maggie. I think I
have something for you, okay?
- Just wait here.
- Do you have a bathroom...
No. Please don't bring
the paint in, okay?
- It's not that bad, man.
- Take it easy, man.
There's almost nothing on
you, man. You look fine.
That will come out. I mean, the
real major cleanup is the floor.
You're such a dick.
- Looks like it just grazed you.
- It doesn't look that bad.
You're right.
Let's hug it out.
- Hugs?
- What's he talking about?
- Hugs.
- What?
Stay away from the kid.
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
You have a lovely body, Owen.
Fuck me.
Do you work out?
Can I ask you where
you got your underwear?
Because they fit. They
fit perfectly like...
You guys are so fucking funny.
I'm asking you a serious
question, that's all.
These should all fit you.
All I need is a T-shirt and some pants.
Take it all.
I don't need all this.
She didn't have to give me all this.
Just take it all, man.
- I don't have to bring it back?
- Jesus. Are you listening? Take the clothes.
- I was just fucking asking.
- Take them.
Do you want to help your friend?
Now it's his turn.
- Stay strong, Private.
- Yes, sir.
Fuck!
Don't give them anything!
Private!
Your life depends on it!
Please.
Fuck! Motherfuckers! I
will fucking kill you!
Christ!
My name is Private Joe Willis. I'm
with the United States Marine Corps.
I was told I was coming
here to fight for my country.
But now I realize that
Afghanistan belongs to its people.
And we have no business being here.
I love you, Cassie.
Joe Jr., your daddy always loves you.
You have two daughters.
Okay. Dad, get down.
- How's this?
- Perfect.
- Great. Great.
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Happy birthday!
Happy birthday!
- You like the kitchen?
- I love it.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mom, this is from Deedee.
- Thank you, Deedee.
- You're welcome.
- Can I help you open it?
- Yes, please.
- She looking now?
- No, she's opening the presents.
Good job on the kitchen.
What did he just say to me?
He said you did a good
job on the kitchen.
Okay. Go, go.
Blow out the candles. Come on, come on.
Do it.
- Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday, Mama.
- Thank you.
Maggie? Maggie.
- No!
- Maggie, slow down.
Maggie, be careful.
What are you doing?
I want to get to the ice before my mama.
Well, you better wait
for her, don't you think?
Everybody loves Maggie.
- Why do you say that?
- Because she's lovable.
You know, your dad saved me
in that water, right there,
when we were both kids.
You know, you're like your dad.
Am I?
Am I like my mom?
A spitting image, yeah.
Except you're yourself,
Isabelle. And everybody loves you.
Come on.
I did it!
I talked to her for over an hour.
She said to me that she hadn't
slept right in over three years.
She kept having these nightmares
that I would come back and shoot her.
I don't know.
I told her it was all right,
that I wasn't gonna hurt her.
She just started to cry.
Right there in the bank,
she just started to cry.
And she thanked me.
She said that she felt like...
What did she say?
Like she could breathe again.
And then she asked if I wanted
to open up a bank account.
No.
I swear to God.
- What did you do?
- I opened an account.
I'm proud of you.
I can't wait to start bouncing checks.
When I was like 17 or 18,
I used to listen to this song,
like, over and over again.
Me, too.
Really?
Why is that so surprising?
I don't know. I just...
I took you more for,
like, an 'NSync fan.
Fuck you.
Give me that.
- Really?
- Really.
You think I'm such a square.
I'm starting to reassess, Snoop Dogg.
Just because I was a
cheerleader, it doesn't...
Yeah, and you dated a football player.
I am such a cliché.
You were kind of a pain in
the ass. You got to admit that.
No, I wasn't.
Guys always say that girls are
stuck up if they won't talk to them.
I just didn't like you.
You were always drunk and fighting...
I have to get some air.
Captain!
Take it.
What do we do?
He has no value for us.
Just a weight on our shoulder.
Waste of food and water.
Kill him.
Pick it up.
You have family?
Do you want to see them again?
Pick up the pipe!
- Captain...
- It's you or him.
Kill him or I will kill you.
Kill him! Kill him or
I will cut his head off!
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him!
Shit.
I brought you some molding.
Hey, look, I don't want to
ruin anything, all right.
I just want to be able to
come over and see the girls.
Please, I would love you
to come see the girls.
We just miss Sam.
Yeah.
That's Hank.
You still at it, huh?
Where did you ever learn to be so handy?
Cover there!
Move forward. Moving forward!
Come on. Let's go.
Straight ahead!
- Stop right there!
- Get your hands up.
Come to me. Come to me.
Come on. Get your hands up.
Get your hands up. Right here. Get down.
You a Marine?
Cahill, is that your name?
Was there anyone else with you?
- Come on. Ready?
- Come on.
Get it on. Get it on.
We need a nose.
- Mom, nose.
- Nose.
- Nose!
- Here.
Get the nose. Get the nose.
He is looking hot, you guys.
Can you teach them
how to throw snowballs?
Because they can't even hit me.
That one hit you.
Maybe I should hit you
with a massive snowball.
Come on.
Izzie, Izzie, are you okay?
Izzie, Izzie. Hey, hey, hey.
- Are you okay?
- Grace.
Sucker! Sucker.
Get him! Get him!
Get him. Try and get him.
Hello?
Yes, this is she.
See this cheater-pants over here.
Come on. You freaked me out.
- What?
- Not me.
It was him! Get up.
Hey. What's going on?
- Uncle Tommy, she grabbed my hair.
- Okay.
I'm sorry. I want to keep playing.
Okay. What?
- Can I go out?
- Not yet.
- Why?
- Because we have to be patient. Okay?
- Sir.
- Welcome home, Sam.
Thanks.
Daddy!
- I missed you so much.
- I missed you, too.
My babies.
I love you, honey.
- Here, let me take your bag.
- Sure.
Come on. Come on. Hurry.
Do you like it? Do you like it?
Wow. It's amazing.
I think he likes it.
- Who did it?
- Me.
- You did?
- And Uncle Tommy.
Uncle Tommy and 'three amigos'.
Are you tired, honey?
Come, get in bed. Everyone.
This is fun.
- I missed you, Daddy.
- Me, too.
My girls.
That's us, all right.
Can I get up, Mom?
Dad, it's not bedtime.
I locked that door.
It's broken.
I'm just gonna finish shaving.
- Banged up well, huh?
- Yeah.
Can't you take that
down to the mechanic?
I got it.
Nothing else to do.
You okay?
Yeah.
'Cause after I got back from Nam,
I couldn't talk to your mother.
I guess I took it out on
you and Tommy, you know, I...
I don't know why.
Look, if you ever wanna
talk, let me know. All right?
You okay?
You're good.
Better than I thought, yeah.
You look good out there with them.
Thanks for taking care of them.
I didn't expect that.
It just comes naturally, you know.
It makes me start to think, you know.
Grace is something, huh?
Did you fuck her?
What? You kidding?
I'd understand.
- You thought I was dead.
- Stop it.
Tommy,
I could forgive you.
What's going on in your head?
What's making you think that?
You guys just look like two
teenagers in love out there.
All right.
I mean, you know?
You can't deny that.
You can tell me.
You gotta tell me. You understand?
- I know you slept in my house.
- Sam. Sam...
Hey, don't bullshit me.
Joe Jr., come back.
Cassie, he's fine.
Ever since his dad died, I
can't let him out of my sight.
Look at him. He's got a mind of his own.
I have this nightmare where
Joe is looking up at me,
and he's trying to tell me something.
He's trying to talk
to me, but the teeth,
his teeth just fall out of
his mouth and there is blood,
and I'm scrabbling
around picking them up.
And then last night,
your husband was there.
And he looks at my hand,
and he takes my hand,
and he looks at my wedding
ring and he just smiles at me.
- Did he say anything?
- No. He just smiled.
In the dream, I hated
him for being alive.
That's why I came over
to apologize. I'm sorry.
I'm sick of feeling like this all
the time. I want to forgive them.
I want to be able to forgive them.
Poor Joe Jr.
He knows.
He's just like his daddy. He
knows exactly what I'm thinking.
Where are you going, huh?
- Sam.
- Hi.
Did you see him die?
No.
Did you hear anything?
I mean, was he on his own?
He was brave. I know that.
That's Captain Cahill.
He was friends with your daddy.
Wave. Are you gonna
wave? Are you gonna wave?
You're a good man.
Baby, where are you going? Come here.
- Sir, Captain Cahill.
- Send him in.
I want to go back, sir.
I'm ready. Need to see my men.
How's the counseling going?
Yeah. I saw Thompson.
Everything pretty good there and,
you know, just thinking about my men
and want to get back.
That's good.
How's the family?
I can't be there, sir.
Yeah?
They don't understand.
You know, I mean, nobody understands.
It's gonna take a little time, Sam.
You've been through a lot of shit.
So has your family.
I don't mind Brian.
He never hits people, only
the boys, but not the girls.
- That is nice.
- Yeah.
And he has a dog with really big ears.
I can't remember his name, though.
Elephant?
An elephant's not a dog.
I know an elephant's not a dog.
Then why did you say it?
Because elephants have big
ears and so does his dog.
So, big ears, get it?
It's really funny if
you think about it, Dad.
Sam, relax.
But how is it funny?
Big ears.
- Is Dad okay, Mom?
- Yeah. Of course. Of course.
When is Uncle Tommy coming?
- He's coming soon, sweetie, okay?
- Okay.
He wants to play with you.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- I'm gonna go check on Daddy, okay?
Sammy, what happened?
What's going on?
Talk to me.
What happened?
What did they do to you?
What happened with you and Tommy?
We kissed. That's it.
I missed you.
I thought you were dead.
I couldn't get out of bed.
That's it.
- You told me the truth?
- You know.
Now tell me.
I think you're fucking Tommy.
Sam...
Come on, come on. Faster. Faster.
Why did you stop pulling?
Hey.
You girls playing?
What's wrong?
It's okay.
I was just confused.
It's gonna be okay.
Come here. Give me a hug.
Now. Those are my girls.
Why did the girl blush when
she opened the refrigerator?
- She saw the salad dressing.
I told you guys that one?
A thousand times.
It's still funny, though.
Have fun.
Where have you been?
I was outside
just thinking and...
I was just thinking
about you and the kids
and the sun came up and I thought,
I'm so lucky to be alive.
We're gonna be late. Come on.
Do you have a spelling test today?
Come on, Grandpa. It's my
birthday. It's my birthday!
Can I open my presents now? Please.
I think we should wait.
Wait for Uncle Tommy.
- Pretty please.
- Well, let her open just one. It won't hurt.
- You can open Grandpa's.
- Thank you.
Just one.
- Okay, Mom.
- Let me show you which it is.
Is it the big one?
It's Uncle Tommy!
Let's guess.
Izzie.
- Hey.
What's the matter?
Is she okay?
- Hi.
- Grace, this is Tina.
- I'm Tina.
- Nice to meet you.
- This is my brother's wife, Grace.
We're all in the dining room.
Oh, my God. She's so pretty.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
This is Tina.
She's an old friend.
Actually, we just met an hour ago.
Yeah. It was like an hour and a half.
You got quite a charmer here.
It hides inside its shell
putting its head in the
shell and its arms and legs
and its little tiny tail.
And when the thing that's
scaring him goes like this,
the turtle doesn't come out.
So, the thing that scares
the turtle goes away
'cause it thinks it's a rock.
- You are a smart girl.
- Happy birthday.
Yes, you are.
- Be careful.
- Everyone needs some reassurance.
Everyone's different, Dad, you know.
- Stop playing with your cake.
- What do you mean?
I just think it's necessary that
everybody has someone to listen to them.
Right, you know, these days they
need therapy if they stub their toe.
These guys are Marines.
They're trained for it.
They're Marines, but
they're still people,
and I don't think that anybody
is trained to shoot somebody.
What do you think they are trained for?
I think that they're... What?
They're trained to use deadly force...
- Trained to kill. ...but
nobody can really be trained
to watch someone die.
That's just something
that you're not taught.
Hey.
Isabelle, let it go.
Please. Thank you.
So, what do you do?
- I'm going to be a nurse.
- Hey!
- I'm in nursing school.
- Give it. Give it.
- Dad?
- Isabelle.
That's my kitty.
- You're a nurse?
- I'm a nurse, sir.
- Need a nurse?
- Let you know if I do.
Maggie gets everything.
- She got the best doll.
- It's her birthday, honey.
I didn't get anything that
I wanted on my birthday.
And you were in stupid Afghanistan.
Nursing. How's nursing
been for you, Tina?
It's been a challenge.
My stepfather actually encouraged me.
Where did you grow up, Tina?
Just 20 miles south. Actually,
I've never really left.
So... I'm gonna change that, though.
I'm living at home right now which...
It's kind of my home because nobody
else is really there most of the time,
which is good, it helps me
save money for school and stuff.
- RN?
- An RN, yeah.
I have another year to go,
but hopefully my grades...
Isabelle, we're trying to
listen to our guest, all right?
So you're in eight-hour
shifts, 12-hour...
Now I am praying for 12-hour
shifts. I have to get...
Student loans are killing me.
I don't know how anyone
does it. How did you do it?
Isabelle.
Stop it.
What got you into it?
I genuinely like people and I love...
I might as well like it.
Enough!
Couldn't you just stay dead?
Isabelle!
You're just mad 'cause Mom would
rather sleep with Uncle Tommy than you.
Isabelle! Why would you say that?
Mom and Uncle Tommy
had sex all the time.
Enough!
Can I go home now?
I wanna go to bed.
Sorry, Mom.
Why did you say that?
You know it's not true.
I don't like Dad.
I'd rather have Uncle
Tommy around instead of Dad.
Me, too.
Daddy's gonna be better, okay?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Thanks, Mom.
- Mom, I love you.
- I love you, baby.
Elsie, I don't know what he's gonna do.
Where are you going?
It's none of your damn
business, you know.
Just stay the hell out of it.
You gotta call the police, Hank.
What is that?
- Where are the kids?
- In bed.
- They all tucked in?
- Yeah.
Say their prayers?
Good.
Sam?
What am I supposed to do now, Grace?
- You know what I did to get back to you?
- No.
You know what I did to
fucking get back to you?
You fucking bitch!
You know how he fucking suffered?
He fucking suffered because of you!
And what have you done to my fucking
house and my fucking kids, Grace?
- You're fucking my brother.
- Sam, you know I didn't.
You're fucking my brother
in my fucking house!
- Sam, please.
- I love you, Grace!
- Please, our girls, please.
- You know how much I love you?
You know what I... Grace,
do you know what I fucking...
You know what I had to do with
these fucking hands, Grace?
You... Fuck!
God, fuck!
What are you doing here?
Come on, man.
- Hey. Hey. Hey, hey.
- What are you fucking doing?
Go to your room.
- Fuck. What are you doing, Tommy?
- Okay.
- What the fuck are you doing to me?
- Girls, lock the door.
Behind my fucking back!
- Did you call the cops?
- Hold on.
- Did you call the fucking cops?
- All right. All right. All right.
Is there a disturbance?
Hold back.
What are you doing here?
- Drop your weapon.
- What are you doing?
- Hold on. Put your gun down.
- Tommy, go back in the house.
- What are you doing, huh?
- Put your weapon down, Captain.
You know me?
- Just shut up for a second, okay?
- You know me, huh?
- I know your father, sir.
- Stay back!
- All right. All right. All right.
- You're a war hero, sir.
- I'm no fucking hero!
I'm no fucking hero!
You know what I've done?
- Hey, it's all right. Sam!
- Just relax.
- Sam!
- Put the gun down, Sam.
- Put the gun down.
- What are you gonna do?
You gonna shoot me?
- Put the gun down!
- Sam!
- Fucking shoot me! Shoot me!
- Hold your fire. Nobody shoot!
Shoot me! Come on!
Jesus, shut the fuck up! This
is a family matter. Shut up!
Shut up. He's my brother.
- Just stop for a second.
- Put the gun down, sir.
- Just let me talk to him. He's my brother.
- Give him a minute.
- Sam!
- You are my brother, Sam!
Sam!
You're my brother. You're my family.
Do you hear me?
Sam!
What's going on, Sam?
I'm drowning, Tommy.
Go. Go, go. Get on the ground!
- Gun clear. Get down.
- Get on the ground now!
Get down!
- Give me your hand.
On your knees. On your knees.
Get him up.
My darling Grace,
if you're reading this, it
means I didn't make it back.
Nothing is certain in this life.
The only thing I know for sure
is that I love you and our girls.
That is the only thing I know.
- Hello?
- Hey, Tommy. It's Sam.
Hey.
I was just thinking about you.
- You all right?
- Yeah. I'm good.
Just calling. Yeah.
You're my brother, Tommy.
When is your birthday, Uncle Tommy?
Okay, sir. You know the drill.
We'll see you in about 30 minutes.
Sam, tell me what happened.
Sam, what happened?
Why are you punishing yourself?
I've loved you since I was 16 years old.
You know that?
If you don't tell me what happened,
you're not gonna see me again.
I killed him.
I killed Joe Willis.
I don't know who said, "Only the
dead have seen the end of war."
I have seen the end of war.
The question is, can I live again?