(MOTORCYCLE REVVING) (SIRENS WAILING)
(TIRES SCREECHING) (HORNS HONKING)
(VEHICLE CRASHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(MAN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MAN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Almost.
"Almost."
Sir, with all due respect,
are you sure this is our best option?
I mean, why can't we just correct the problem?
Because my fuckin' nephew
killed a dog.
And he stole a car.
A car
which currently is among our inventory.
So we're giving everything up for a car?
It's not just a car.
It is John Wick's car.
Oh.
(DOOR LOCK BUZZES)
(STAMMERING)
Sir, why don't we just give it back?
He killed my nephew.
(GASPS)
My brother.
And a dozen of my men.
Over his car.
And a puppy.
And you... (SPITS)
You think he will stop now?
Hmm?
LIEUTENANT: Sir, he's one man.
Why don't we just eliminate him?
John Wick
is a man of focus...
Commitment...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
And sheer fuckin' will!
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
He once killed three men in a bar...
With a pencil. I know. I've heard the story.
With a fucking pencil!
Who the fuck can do that?
I can assure you
that the stories you hear about this man,
if nothing else, has been watered down.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(JOHN SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(CALL DISCONNECTS)
(SPEAKS RUSSIAN)
(MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(KEYS JINGLE)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(MEN YELLING)
(MAN YELLING)
(BULLETS RICOCHETING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
(MEN YELLING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(JOHN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(MAN GROANING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(CHUCKLES)
Mr. Wick.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(DOG PANTING)
Hey, buddy.
Hey.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Good dog.
What are you doing, John?
JOHN: Looking at you.
What are you doing?
HELEN: I'm waiting for you.
Come here.
Hey, boy.
(SIGHS)
Nice peaceful place you got here.
Hey, Aurelio. Hey.
John, what the hell? I thought you loved this car.
What do you think?
Well, your motor's about to fall out
and the chassis's all bent up,
the driveshaft is all destroyed.
And I don't know if you noticed,
but you got a crack in your windshield.
I mean... What do I think?
I could fix this.
Thanks for finding her.
Not a problem, man. I just made a few calls.
No big deal.
Let me know when it's fixed.
All right. It'll be ready Christmas...
2030.
(DOORBELL DINGING)
(DINGING CONTINUES)
Ciao, John.
Santino.
(BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(OFFERS COFFEE IN ITALIAN)
(THANKS HIM IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Good to see you.
Good to see you.
I was sorry to hear about your wife, John.
Thank you.
SANTINO: Hi.
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) And the dog, does he have a name?
No.
Listen, John, with all sincerity...
I don't want to be here.
Please, don't.
I'm asking you not to do this.
I'm sorry.
No one gets out and comes back
without repercussions.
I do this with a heavy heart, John.
But remember, if not for what I did
on the night of your impossible task,
you wouldn't be here right now, like this.
This is because of me.
This, in part, is mine.
Take it back.
"Take it back"? Take it back.
A marker is no small thing, John.
For a man to grant a marker to another,
is to bind a soul to a blood oath.
Find someone else.
Listen to me.
What is this? Hmm?
Do you remember? This is your blood.
You came to me. I helped you.
And if you don't do this,
you know the consequences.
I'm not that guy anymore.
You are always that guy, John.
I can't help you.
I'm sorry.
Yes. You're right.
You can't.
But he can.
I'll see you soon, John.
You have a beautiful home, John.
(BIDS FAREWELL IN ITALIAN)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(EXPLOSION)
(DOG WHIMPERING)
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Well, good evenin', John.
Hey, Jimmy.
Gas leak?
Yeah, gas leak.
You workin' again?
I'll see you, Jimmy.
Come on, boy. (DOG WHIMPERS)
Good night, John.
Oh, shit.
I'd like to see the manager.
How good to see you again so soon, Mr. Wick.
Shall I announce you?
Yes, please.
Stay.
(EXTENSION LINE BEEPS)
Mr. Wick is on his way to see you, sir.
(SIGHS)
Impeccable.
(COINS CLINKING) Put these into circulation.
Where is he?
Thank you, my friend.
Beautiful work. Beautiful.
What are you doing, Jonathan?
He burned my house down.
You rejected his marker. You're lucky he stopped there.
What the hell were you thinking,
giving a marker to a man like Santino D'Antonio?
It was the only way I could get out.
Oh. You call this "out"?
What did you think was gonna happen?
What did you expect? Huh?
Did you really think this day was never going to come? Hmm?
What does he want you to do?
I didn't ask.
I just said no.
(SIGHS)
Two rules that cannot be broken, Jonathan.
No blood on Continental grounds,
and every marker must be honored.
Now, while my judgment comes in the form of excommunicado,
the High Table demand a more severe outcome
if their traditions are refused.
I have no choice?
You dishonor the marker, you die.
You kill the holder of the marker, you die.
You run, you die.
This is what you agreed to, Jonathan.
Do what the man asks.
Be free.
Then, if you want to go after him,
burn his house down, be my guest.
But until then...
Rules.
Exactly. Rules.
Without them, we'd live with the animals.
Do you board?
I'm sorry to say, sir, but this facility does not.
I, however, would be willing to accept
the responsibility, should you wish.
Appreciate that.
Does he have a name, sir?
No.
Good dog. (DOG WHIMPERS)
Stay. (DOG WHIMPERS)
(HORNS HONKING)
SANTINO: This was my father's collection.
I see little more than just paint on canvas, of course.
But I do find myself here.
Please.
I didn't want to do this, John.
Had you stayed retired, I would have respected it.
Look at you.
You're thinkin' about it, aren't you?
You're counting exits, guards...
Could you get to me in time?
How would you do it, I wonder?
That woman's pen?
His cane?
Maybe his glasses?
My hands.
Ah. (CHUCKLES)
How exciting.
Yet, you know you cannot, can you?
I told you I needed that guy,
the way you are looking at me right now.
I needed the Boogeyman.
I needed John Wick.
Just tell me what you want.
I want you to kill my sister.
Why?
There are 12 seats at the High Table.
Camorra, Mafia, and Ndrangheta.
The Chinese, the Russian.
When my father died...
He willed his seat to her.
She represents Camorra now.
And I can't help but wonder
what I might accomplish in her stead.
You want me to kill Gianna D'Antonio?
I could never do it.
She is my blood.
I still love her.
JOHN: It can't be done.
She's in Rome for her coronation.
You will take the catacombs in...
It doesn't matter where she is.
That's why I need the ghost, lo spettro, John Wick.
That's why I need you.
Do this for me,
and your marker is honored.
What say you?
Never one to waste words.
Fifty-nine, zero, 3.5.
(KEYS JINGLING)
(BOX UNLOCKS)
(SCREAMS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SPEAKING HEBREW)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
MAN: Jonathan!
JOHN: Julius.
Ciao. Nice to see you.
I fail to recall the last time you were in Rome.
And here I'd heard
you had retired.
I had.
Then humor me with but one question.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) No.
All right, then.
One of our finest rooms.
(THANKS HIM IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) And enjoy your stay.
Mr. Wick.
Is the sommelier in?
I have never known him not to be.
Good afternoon, Mr. Wick.
It's been a long time.
I'd like a tasting.
I am quite excited to show you something.
First...
Buongiorno, Signor Wick.
Ciao, Angelo.
Welcome back to Rome.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
I am.
I know of your past fondness for the German varietals,
but I can wholeheartedly endorse the new breed of Austrians.
Glock .34 and .26.
This is the original map of the D'Antonio estate.
Here, you have all the ancient ruins.
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
Tell me, Mr. Wick, is this a formal event or a social affair?
Social.
And is this for day or evening?
I need one for day and one for night.
SOMMELIER: Recontoured grips.
Flared magwell for easier reloads.
And I know you'll appreciate the custom porting.
What's next?
I need something robust. Precise.
"Robust. Precise."
This is the map of the temple and catacombs underneath.
In what style? Italian.
How many buttons? Two.
Trousers? Tapered.
How about the lining?
Tactical.
AR-15, 11.5-inch.
Compensated with an ion-bonded bolt carrier.
Trijicon accupoint with one-six magnification.
And this is the modern blueprint.
There are one, two, three gates.
TAILOR: Silicon carbide discs. Ceramic matrices.
Accompanying laminates.
Cutting-edge body armor.
We just sew it between the fabric and the lining.
Zero penetration. However...
Quite painful, I'm afraid.
Could you recommend anything for the end of the night?
Something big, bold.
May I suggest the Benelli M4?
Custom bolt carrier release and charging handle.
Textured grips, should your hands get wet.
An Italian classic.
Dessert?
(SIGHS) Dessert.
The finest cutlery. All freshly stoned.
JOHN: Well done.
Could you do a rush order? I sure can.
Where would you like to have it sent?
The hotel.
Shall I have everything sent to your room?
Yes. Thank you. Excellent.
Mr. Wick?
Do enjoy your party.
(BELL TOLLING)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMAN VOCALIZING)
(GUN COCKS)
(WHISPERS INDISTINCTLY)
(VOCALIZING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Good evening.
Are you enjoying the party?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(INAUDIBLE)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Mr. Akoni.
Are you enjoying the festivities?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(CHUCKLES)
(IN ENGLISH) Please. Sit.
Ms. D'Antonio,
you can't just take what is rightfully mine.
Nothing was taken.
Those among your own came to us with these territories.
A knife was pressed to their throats.
Semantics.
Besides...
That blade you speak of was meant for their children.
They were only meant to watch.
What is yours is now ours, Mr. Akoni.
Now go.
Enjoy the party.
Have some fun.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) John.
Gianna.
There was a time not so long ago
in which I considered us as friends.
I still do.
GIANNA: Yet here you are.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) What brought you back, John?
A marker.
Held by?
Your brother.
Tell me, John.
This marker...
Is it how you got out?
And what was her name,
this woman whose life has ended my own?
Helen.
"Helen."
This Helen...
Was she worth the price that you now seek to pay?
Now,
let me tell you what happens when I die.
Santino will lay claim to my seat at the Table.
He will take New York.
And you will have been the one who gifted it to him.
What would your Helen think about that, John?
What would your Helen think about you?
Hmm?
Why?
Because I lived my life my way.
And I will die my way.
Do you fear damnation, John?
Yes.
You know,
I always thought I could escape it.
That I'd see it coming.
That I'd see you.
(GUNSHOT FIRES)
(MUSIC PLAYING) (PEOPLE CHEERING)
John?
Cassian.
You working?
Yeah.
You?
Good night?
Afraid so.
I'm sorry to hear that.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER COMM LINKS)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING) (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
Loose ends?
(SMACKS LIPS)
Yeah...
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(BULLETS RICOCHETING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUNFIRE)
(MAN YELLS)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(MAN GROANS)
(JOHN GROANS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(PANTING)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MAN GROANS)
(GUN CLICKS) (YELLING AND GROANING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
(BULLET RICOCHETS)
(YELLS)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING)
(MAN GROANS)
(JOHN PANTING)
(CAR APPROACHING)
(JOHN GRUNTING)
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
You're not havin' a good night, are you, John?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(BOTH YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
JULIUS: Gentlemen!
Gentlemen!
(BOTH PANTING)
Do I need to remind you
that there will be no business
conducted on the Continental grounds?
No, signore.
No, sir.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Now, may I suggest a visit to the bar,
so you can calm yourselves.
Gin, wasn't it?
Yes.
Bourbon, right?
Yeah.
(THANKING IN ITALIAN)
(SIGHS)
I had a marker.
Whose?
Her brother.
I see.
You had no choice.
He wants her seat at the Table.
He'll get it now.
Yeah.
So you're free. (EXHALES)
Am I?
No.
Not at all.
You killed my ward. Someone I was close to.
An eye for an eye, John.
You know how it goes.
Yeah.
I'll make it quick.
I promise.
I appreciate that.
I'll try and do the same.
This round's on me.
Consider it a professional courtesy.
No. Thanks.
(SIGHS)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
SANTINO: Hello, John.
I understand if you are upset.
And I know it might feel personal.
But what kind of man would I be
if I didn't avenge my sister's murder?
(PHONE HANGS UP)
John?
Could you let management know
I'll be checking out in the morning.
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
(LINE RINGING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING) (INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Operator. How may I direct your call?
Accounts payable. OPERATOR: One moment, please.
Accounts payable. How may I help you?
SANTINO: I'd like to open an account.
Name on the account? John Wick.
OPERATOR: Verification?
SANTINO: 9305-05.
OPERATOR: State of contract?
Open. Denomination?
Seven million.
Processing. Please hold.
I appreciate the service. My pleasure.
You will find safe passage below.
Transportation is waiting for you.
May you have a safe journey, Mr. Wick.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(TYPEWRITERS CLACKING) (TELEPHONES RINGING)
(CELL PHONES RINGING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Order confirmed.
What is this? He completed the task.
The marker is over.
Mark it.
If Mr. Wick isn't dead already,
he soon will be.
Will you mark it, sir?
You have no idea what's coming, do you?
SANTINO: I have everyone in New York looking for him.
I doubt we will see him again.
Do you now?
You stabbed the devil in the back
and forced him back into the life that he had just left.
You incinerated the priest's temple.
Burned it to the ground.
Now he's free of the marker, what do you think he'll do?
He had a glimpse of the other side
and he embraced it.
But you, Signor D'Antonio...
...took it away from him.
He was already back.
Oh, he came back for love, not for you.
He owed me. I had every right.
And now he's coming again.
He did tell you not to do this.
He did warn you.
(BIDS FAREWELL IN ITALIAN)
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING) (JOHN YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(WOMAN YELLS)
(GROANING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BONE SNAPPING) (WOMAN SCREAMS)
(YELLING)
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(SIGHS)
(MAN YELLS)
(GAGGING)
(MAN GROANING)
(GRUNTING LOUDLY)
(NECK SNAPS)
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
(MAN GROANING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(MAN YELLS)
(MAN GROANING)
ANNOUNCER: (OVER PA SYSTEM) Please notify MTA personnel of any suspicious activity.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER 1: Your attention, please.
The Broad Street bound C train is now arriving.
Your attention, please.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER 2: Next stop, Canal Street.
(DOORS CHIME)
This is Canal Street.
This is the Broad Street bound C Train.
The next stop is Rector Street.
This is Rector Street.
This is the Broad Street bound C Train.
The next stop is Broad Street.
(GROANING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(KNIFE CLATTERS)
(GROANS)
(GROANS LOUDLY)
This is Broad Street.
This is the last stop on the southbound C train.
The blade is in your aorta.
You pull it out, you'll bleed, and you will die.
This is the end of the line.
Consider this a professional courtesy.
This is Broad Street.
This is the last stop on the southbound C Train.
This is the end of the line.
(DOORS CHIME)
(HOMELESS MAN MUMBLING)
HOMELESS MAN: We say things, we see things.
The things you see are nightmares, man.
Like this one time...
Take me to him.
Tell him it's John Wick.
You know, they just... They put it in everything!
Hey, man. You got a quarter? (SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
(DOG WHINES)
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(MAN COUGHING)
(PIGEONS COOING)
BOWERY KING: As I live and breathe!
John Wick.
The man.
The myth.
The legend. (CHUCKLES)
You're not very good at retiring.
I'm workin' on it.
Mr. Wick doesn't remember, but we met many years ago,
before my ascension...
When I was just a pawn in the game.
We met and you gave me a gift,
the gift that would make me a king.
You don't remember, but there I was, standing in an alleyway.
I didn't even hear you comin'.
You gave me this.
Gift from the Boogeyman.
Perfect for every occasion.
But you also gave me a choice.
Pull my gun, shoot you in the back, and die.
Or keep the pressure on my neck...
...and live.
And so you see, I survived.
No one sneaks up on me anymore, thanks to you.
I am all-seeing and all-knowing.
Then you know why I'm here.
(CHUCKLES) Santino D'Antonio, yes.
Your contract went wide, John.
That's bad for your health.
What's the number up to now, Earl?
$7 million! Damn!
It's Christmas. We're going to Applebee's after this.
JOHN: I need your help.
You have eyes begging for change on every corner in the city.
I'm thinkin' you can find Santino.
I need you to move me. Underground.
Get me to him.
How sweet it is!
The Boogeyman begging me for help.
Well, of course, John.
Yes, John. Whatever you'd like, John.
Would you like a back rub with that, John?
You're going to help me.
Why the fuck would I do that?
Because I'm the only one that can help you.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
You're gonna help me out?
That's downright upright of you, Mr. Wick.
You sound positively magnanimous.
But look around you.
How much help does it look like I need?
It seems to me that the real question, Mr. Wick,
is who in this cruel world of ours is going to help you?
There's a storm coming.
Not just for me. For all of us.
For everyone under the Table.
Yes, killing someone who has a seat at the High Table
does create a problem.
But it's your problem, baby.
After all, none of my people sent Gianna D'Antonio
to the hereafter.
That being said, Santino has her seat now.
And he wants the city.
When he's done uptown, you think he's gonna stop at 14th Street?
We'll just have to take care of ourselves.
Oh, yeah? For how long?
And how much blood?
You kill Santino,
the Camorra, and the High Table come for you.
I kill Santino, they come for me.
He's offered $7 million for your life.
$7 million is a lot of money, Mr. Wick.
So I guess you have a choice.
You want a war?
Or do you wanna just give me a gun?
(CHUCKLES)
Somebody, please! Get this man a gun!
Kimber 1911, .45 ACP.
Seven-round capacity.
Seven rounds?
$7 million gets you seven rounds.
That's a million dollars a round, baby.
Let's go.
Your descent into Hell begins here, Mr. Wick.
He's at the museum.
Earl will guide you.
Do be careful on your way down.
Oh, and remember, you owe me.
You don't want me owing you.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
SANTINO: Welcome, everyone.
Let us toast to the future of the High Table
and of course, to the memory of my dear sister.
(ALL TOASTING IN ITALIAN)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Nice to see you.
(GREETING IN ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Mr. Akoni, how are you?
(MUSIC STOPS)
(MEN YELLING)
(YELLS)
Wick is here.
Yeah.
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOTS FIRING IN DISTANCE)
You and you, with me. You, go.
(GRUNTS)
(MEN GROANING)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(GRUNTS) (GROANS)
(GROANS)
WOMAN: (OVER PA) Welcome to "Reflections of the Soul" at the New Modern NYC.
Within this exhibition,
the interplay of light and the nature of self-images
coalesce to provide an experience
which will highlight the fragility
of our perception of space and our place within it.
We hope through this exhibit we can provide new insights
into your understanding of the world,
and just possibly lead you to deeper reflection
into the nature of self.
(SANTINO SPEAKING ITALIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) The marker is complete, John.
You should have just run away.
You know what the Camorra will do to you.
You think you're Old Testament?
No, John.
No.
Killing me won't stop the contract.
Killing me will make it so much worse.
John,
you know what I think?
I think you are addicted to it.
To the vengeance.
(MEN YELLING)
Welcome to "Reflections of the Soul" at the New Modern NYC.
SANTINO: No wife.
No life.
No home.
Vengeance, it's all you have.
You wanted me back.
I'm back.
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(GROANS)
(BOTH STRAINING)
You are now exiting "Reflections of the Soul" at the New Modern NYC.
We hope that your journey through the exhibit
has been one of reflective contemplation
allowing for a new perspective and insight.
You are now exiting "Reflections of the Soul..."
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BONES CRACKING) (SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(JOHN SPEAKING)
You are now exiting "Reflections of the Soul..."
Good evening.
Is the manager in?
The manager is always in.
Winston.
Mr. D'Antonio.
Your evening has been colorful, I see.
Seeking safe harbor, I presume?
I want his membership revoked. Now.
In the eyes of this institution,
Mr. Wick has breached no legalities.
Then you know that I have the right to demand of you...
Nothing. You demand nothing of me, Mr. D'Antonio.
This kingdom is mine and mine alone.
All right.
Then enjoy your kingdom, Winston, while you still can.
And you its privileges, sir.
I'm here to see Santino D'Antonio.
He's waiting for you in the lounge, sir.
Duck fat.
Makes all the difference.
WINSTON: Jonathan...
Have you seen the menu here?
Lot of options. Jonathan, listen to me...
A man can stay here a long time
and never eat the same meal twice.
Jonathan, just walk away.
Yeah, Jonathan.
Walk...
What have you done?
Finished it.
How was he?
He was a good dog. I have enjoyed his company.
(JOHN CHUCKLES)
Let's go home.
(DOG PANTS)
CHARON: Mr. Wick?
If you would be so inclined.
Come on, boy.
It has been a pleasure, Mr. Wick.
Goodbye.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Jonathan.
Winston.
What am I lookin' at?
The Camorra's doubled Santino's open contract.
It's gone international.
High Table?
Mmm-hmm.
And the Continental?
You killed a man on company grounds, Jonathan.
You leave me no choice but to declare you excommunicado.
The doors to any service or provider in connection with the Continental
are now closed to you.
I am so sorry.
Your life is now forfeit.
Then why am I not dead?
Because I deemed it not to be.
Now.
You have one hour. I can't delay it any longer.
You might need this...
Down the road.
JOHN: Winston...
Tell them.
Tell them all.
Whoever comes,
whoever it is,
I'll kill them.
I'll kill them all.
'Course you will.
Jonathan.
Winston.
(CELL PHONE DIALING)
Accounts Payable.
One-one-one-one-one.
In one hour.
John Wick.
Excommunicado.
(TELEPHONES RINGING)
Order 11111 confirmed.
(PIGEONS COOING)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(PANTING)