Subtitles by:
Ben - The Netherlands
! Notice !
English is not my native language,
Please forgive me for any mistakes.
~ Enjoy ~
I'm glad I got away from all this.
I pitty you.
Don't bother.
- Okay.
You want my rep, right?
Then shoot me.
But know this.
You kill me here without
facing me on the street...
you'll be known for what you are...
Scum.
- And you'll be dead.
And me?
I then killed a legend.
Fucking..
A last request, grandad?
- 1 MONTH EARLIER -
What?
- Ahh
Fuck off, huh?
You fucking bitch.
- Ah!
- Uhn..
Ah.
Where do you live, darling?
Ah! Ah!
Tell me, where the fuck
do you live, darling?
She lives over there, c'mon just
fucking leave...
Was he talking to you?
- Alright.
I want your mom to see this.
If she aint gonna teach you any
fucking rules, then I am.
- Aah!
Is there anyone else who
wants to be a grass (snitch)?
This is what happends
when you talk.
- Uh ohhh..
Pay attention.
- Aaahhh!!
Aahhh!
- Aaaah!
I don't want to be doing
shit like this.
Cutting up bitches, and shit.
But this is my square.
My fucking square!
You people better start playing
by my fucking rules, alright?
- I fucking hate you.
I fucking hate you, c'mon.
C'mon!
Get off me.
- You go to the nurse, come.
Get. Off. Me.
- You're coming with me.
Get off me, now.
Get off of me, miss.
- You mind your mouth, young man.
Oh yeah? yeah?
You're gonna regret this,
I swear.
- I don't want to suspend him.
You should,
if it helps.
He needs to learn.
Thank you.
But this is not the kind of conduct
we condone here at Arkequin Park
We don't expect the students to
exhibit such wild behavior.
Thing need to change.
I'm sure it's just boisterous energie.
He's never violent at home.
He's a good natured boy.
But this is not the first
fight he's been in.
Sorry, what is it you are
trying to say about my son?
I'll deal with it.
We all do stupid things when
we are young, I mean...
I know that's not an
excuse, ofcourse, but...
Trust me,
I'll deal with this.
This is a waste of time, the girl
aint gonna speak to us.
We should just pay the scumbags a visit.
That's not how it works.
Well, we should do,
we know what they did.
And our job is to proof it,
or deal with it.
I didn't shank her and his bitch mate
might deserve a beating.
Trust me, Malor, you don't win that way.
- Trust me?
We won't end to fill the
third line of the law.
We should be the one
to administer it.
Good afternoon.
We'd like to talk to you about the
situation that happend with your daughter.
Now, no, no, I've you just listen
because we're trying to help. If you..
That went well.
We should do it my way.
Do me. Do me.
Ooh.
Pull my finger, bro.
She aint gonna fight you.
- You don't know, bro.
Ladies like touching up young boys.
Listen, you little prick.
We know what you did.
Ah, you're old, man.
What, did you get bullied at school?
Was it a classic one?
Or did your powers just fuck off,
when you took your badge?
It's usually one of the two.
Yeah, do you wanna hit me?
Hit me, bro.
I'm here, just hit me.
Come on.
Give me a little whack.
Just a little dig, go on.
Nah, nah, nah don't actually. Yeah, go on.
Give me a little slap, good.
Now, give me a fucking slap.
Yeah.
- Turn around.
Is that all we're doing
down here, guys?
Yeah?
Slashing girls in their face?
Fat boy. Skinny boy.
Fuck off.
Move.
So is this how you get a name?
Coward.
That's what you are.
Common criminal.
You lack the courage to be anything...
Memorable.
Are we done yet?
Here's a guy that's gonna
get away with this shit.
When the guvnors was around...
They would have done you fucking here.
Now they were memorable.
They had everybody's respect.
Something you'll never have.
Yeah boys, you're free to go.
Hello?
- Hey Ange, it's Michelle, can we talk?
Yeah, sorry,
Now is not a good time actually.
Yeah yeah,
tomorrow is better.
Sorry.
Alright, thanks.
Come on babe, you're just standing here
Who was that?
Ugh, it's just some salesman.
They drive me mad.
Do you want a cup?
- Yeah, sure.
Don't you ever, fucking call
this number again.
Do you understand?
Hey Mitch,
you want to see this, mate
Look at this guy.
- Oh, fucking hell.
Straight in.
You'd be outside by now.
You'd be legging it like a geezer.
I would have pissed myself.
I mean, literaly pissed myself.
Actually there on the spot.
He's swinging a fucking chairs.
Man, you've gotta stand strong
when it comes to these things.
What, so you throw something small...
and suddenly he just drops
his chainsaw and surrenders?
Stop talking shit, Paul.
What you reckon in this one?
Would you stand and fight,
or would you leg it?
Shouldn't have got to that.
Should've been stopped
before he got inside.
Yeah, but it's only a small
local pub, aint it?
There aint no security.
Who's gonna stop it?
It's not like he's carrying a knife.
He's had to be walking down the
street with that thing in his hand.
Just traveling down the
road with a chainsaw.
Gotta go to round my nange
and fix shit.
Her chainsaw ran out of battery.
Once you're inside you
gotta work as a unit.
Look at his body position.
He's not in control
of that weapon.
As long as one of
you faces him...
Close enough to get his
attention, but far enough
away to avoid a launch,
then you're in business.
And the other two...
One comes from here.
And one from here.
One attacks from behind.
One goes low.
Simple.
Yeah, saw it in a film somewhere.
Listen, get back to work you boys.
This isn't an olderly camp.
We've got clients to please.
He thinks he's Rambo.
Yeah, give him a beer.
He doesn't have beer over here.
Nah, you know I don't drink beer mate.
I've got subscripts.
It's not about meds,
it's about your misses.
Fuck off.
I'm the guvnor.
What?
The guvnor?
Yeah.
You weren't the fucking
guvnor at City last week.
Hey, take your mind back
to West Ham away.
I saved your fucking life,
as usual.
Ah, fuck you saved my life.
Oi, the guvnor is the boss.
Look at the size of you.
I'll have you.
Is that right?
- Yeah, come here.
- Bing, bing, bing.
You wanna touch me,
or what?
You do that again...
And I'll fill you.
Careful mate, he's our case.
I think the guvnor just
shit himself
- Bye darling.
- Love you.
Have you been talking about me?
- No.
I don't mind,
I quite like it.
Do you reckon I'm a better
than the guvnors?
Uh, I don't care.
Yeah, now, neither do I,
but I heard rumours...
That some oldschool bollocks
now don't like it.
Five, fifty-five, please
Not today.
Now don't believe all the
hairy chest stuff.
It's simple, greens are good
for your football.
Eat these...
And it will make you a better player.
- But I hate 'em.
Just eat it.
- But you don't eat them.
And?
Good boy.
Alright, I gotta pop out
for an hour, or so.
But if these aren't gone by
the time I get back.
No boots.
Oi.
Don't give me that.
You good?
See you in a bit, yeah?
Why are you sweeping?
What did you do at school today?
Not much.
You much have done something.
No mom. Same as yesterday
and the day before.
- Show your mother...
Some fucking respect.
Say sorry.
Sorry.
Mitch, calm down, he's just
being fair to humor.
Jump up and down.
Go on.
- Mitch..
Do it!
Stop it.
What the hell is going on?
Do you want to tell her?
Or should I?
Mitch, what's going on?
Come here.
Come here!
Do you want me to spit
in your face aswell, boy?
What the hell is going on?
Dont you ever let me catch you
doing anything like that ever again.
Now go to your room!
Go on!
Mitch..
Where are the guvnors?
May I help you, lads?
Yeah, maybe.
We're looking for a bunch
of old fuckers..
Who like to call
themself the guvnors.
Have you seen them?
No guvnors in here, son.
Only me.
Is that right?
Who are you?
I think you know who I am.
No.
I give up.
Who are you?
I wrecked a man named Strongman,
didn't I?
Not really.
Have you got any ID?
Are you boys all over 18?
Now aren't ya?
Fuck off.
Alright.
Outside.
Fancy it?
No, I'm alright.
Nah, it's just I don't tend
to brawl with the footsoldiers
I want to have a crack at your boss.
Mitch, right?
He left 20 years ago.
He's miles out, and I don't know where.
So...
Good luck with that.
It's pretty much impossible to
lose people these days.
Haven't you heard of the internet?
Fucking hell, ofcourse you haven't.
It's like a time warp in here.
This used to be the most
feared pub in London, and now...
It looks like a badly
decorated job center.
Do yourself a favor.
Get out.
I think I might buy a pint.
Back off, son.
The guvnors are extinct.
But for the record...
If I was still a player.
You're exactly the kind of dealing shit,
I'd string up for fun.
Yeah, is that right?
Yeah.
Well, you know what, grandad?
I'm a little fucked off with the
tone everyone is taking with me in here.
I came down...
To ask some simple questions.
In truth, I came here in peace.
To show my respect.
Leave and it can stay that way.
But if you don't...
I'll be forced to give you a little
hide of myself.
You're joking.
Fucking hell, who's this?
The walking dead?
Your time is long gone,
old man.
Sit down...
And shut up.
Ow!
Ta-da.
One punch.
You made my fucking day, Mick.
What do you want?
- A cup of tea.
Good man.
Oi boss, come and have
a look at this.
Mitch, this old timer knocks
out this little lyric...
It is exceptional.
If you're alright,
I'm busy.
Oh c'mon boss,
have a bust at this.
Email it to me,
I'll watch it later.
Ba-Boom!
Lads!
Thank you.
G'Morning.
G'Afternoon.
The old Mick,
you've only gone viral.
Viral?
Don't worry, there's
no catching.
Half a million people have seen you
online, smacking that twat.
What?
Last night...
CCTV.
Good.
Coming in this pub like that.
They got no idea.
I mean; There's no hierarchy, is there?
I don't want to rain them in,
not like you.
They should put back conscription.
Wouldn't have done us any good.
I mean, we weren't much
better, were we?
Ah well, you weren't criminals...
I just told you how to
defend yourselfs, that's all.
Things got a bit out of hand.
By coming in here...
You'd make a commitment.
A commitment to the people
who sat next to you.
A commitment to me.
You can come in here night and day.
It could be somewhere you
can call home.
A place,
where you learn life.
But I've got 2 rules.
Number 1:
Any trouble outside...
You'll leave at the door.
You come here to train.
Any drama's...
And you're out.
Number 2:
The people sat next to you...
Are now your family.
Your people.
Your blood.
Family...
Is the most important thing.
Welcome.
I don't know why you
picked these ones up.
I've only given you 50 quid.
- But Ronaldo has got these.
Yeah, but when he started out,
he would have killed for these.
I'll do you a deal, yeah?
You score 30 goals in these this season..
And I'll buy these ones
next year, alright?
- What if I score 40?
Okay look, try them on.
Look, they're just like
mile-boots...
Beautiful.
Clean.
Classic.
- Shit.
Oi!
Anymore of that and
you get no boots, alright?
Now, wrap them up.
Take them to the till.
And lets pay for them, alright?
Hey, bro!
Can you get down over here,
real quick?
Yeah, I just have a little question
about one of them T-shirts down here.
- Which one then?
Euh.. It's just..
If I ever see you outside
this shop again...
I swear to fuck,
I'll cut your throat, alright?
- Yeah.
Is there anything more
to be laughing about?
- No, mate.
Good.
You know, I'm not
ashamed of who I am.
I'm not ashamed of who I was.
But I don't want you
to become me.
You are much
better than that.
I thought you weren't
gonna take me to football?
International is a different.
And we're in a box.
Your great-grand father...
Used to take us to
game on a bus.
He used to carry this
silly little duffle bag...
With a pair of boots in it,
in case the team where a man down.
- Yeah, but what about his shin guards?
Who cares about shin guards,
you can kick a ball and save his life.
And who is gonna pick him out of a crowd?
He wasn't Stanley Petrol.
- Who?
Never mind.
- What about you?
- Where you any good?
They used to call me
"The Made Net Maradona".
- Who?
Diego Maradona.
- No clue.
You are joking.
- No.
Nothing matches this.
You can try and find
the excitement elsewhere...
But it just don't exists.
The nerves.
The tension.
For the next 90 minutes,
anything can happen.
I'm sorry it took me so
long to bring you here, my son.
Look at that.
Oi, you there.
I think you're in the wrong
fucking box, mate.
Go inside.
- Dad, it's fine.
Inside.
Now.
Look, I'm not after any
trouble, alright?
I think you're past that.
What's going on here then?
Top boys reunion.
Where would we be if we
didn't have you, champ?
You would have a family, Steve.
Well, there is only so much
of that shit I can handle.
Well...
I'm gonna go and sit with my boy.
I would introduce you,
but, euhh...
What you gonna say?
This is Bads, we used to kick
the fuck out of eachother.
Exactly.
Look after yourselfs.
I'm gonna beat the fuck
out of that old guy.
I don't give a shit.
Chill,
this guys is...
No one fucking disrespects
me like that!
- Bom.
What?
- Boom.
What?!
What is it?
How the fuck...?
I know you wanna
show of the old fellow.
But we got chance with
the other Guvnors here.
I'll send a little message
of to him first.
I'll go.
Alright.
Tomorrow.
Let me get the old man.
Stay there.
Move!
Can I have a word please, mate?
I heard that you were though.
I want to have a little chat.
I'm an old friend
of your dad.
I want you to tell him...
I'm going after the old man...
And then tell him I'm
coming after him.
Tell him I know where you live.
Now open your fucking mouth.
- No.
No.
Show him that.
Hey, here he is.
Come here.
I wanted to do
that for years.
I never knew you
felt that way.
Not the kisses,
the punch.
That little shit
had it coming.
Right, I know.
What are you having?
Alright, chips for me...
Better sausage for Nil.
No, just give us a normal sausage...
You just make it a better one for me.
You got that, sis?
- Got it.
Apparantly...
We can have those tickets for
every England friendly.
Are you alright?
The kid that did this
wanted you.
The kid came to my
school and said...
I should tell you that he'd
batter the old man.
And you're next.
I'll ask around and find out
what this is about okay? Just eh...
Please don't tell your mother.
Mickey!
Mick!
C'mon you lazy old sob.
Breakfast won't make itself.
Oh no, Mickey.
Mickey!
You fucking!
It's alright...
It's alright.
Hello?
No, not at the moment.
No, I'll speak to
you later.
Okay.
Is someone harassing you?
No, no.
It's fine.
Come on.
- But mom...
Out.
I love you.
What did I tell you
about calling this...
Yeah...
We're all here today
to remember Mickey...
One of the best.
Mick told me to mean it
if he's named Mush.
He said: Mush people...
I thought it was from blacksmith.
You know...
A man who works with iron and steel.
And not a bad description
of his left and right, eh?
But it's a.. It's an older word.
German word.
Schmitten
It means...
Soldier.
That was the Mickey I knew.
Mick was always there for me.
For all of us.
He gave us a place to call home.
He thaught me
everthing I know.
And now he's gone.
Loved his quote's, Mick.
So...
Here...
Here's one for the ferryman.
It's Mark Twain.
Yeah?
The fear of death...
Follows from the fear of life.
The man who has lived fully...
Is prepared to die at any time.
To Mickey.
- To Mickey!
Cheers.
Michelle...
Are you eh?...
Just keep an eye on
eh.. you, alright? Okay.
How did you let this happen?
Excuse me?
Who's the kid?
No, not today.
Not now.
Who is he?
20 years...
No explanation...
No apology...
No nothing.
I ain't come here for
your foregiveness.
I couldn't give a shit what you
or anyone else thinks of me.
I know that.
Don't know that you
want the same thing as me.
So don't fight me on this.
Do this with me.
Well?
Adam Shanko.
He's the wanker Mickey
slapped on the video.
What's his story?
He's a prick.
Why did Mickey get involved?
The kid came in the pub...
Looking for you.
That's another body
on your list.
You do remember Charlie?
Where are the others?
Why aren't they here?
Because I told them
not to come.
Mickey wouldn't have...
He wouldn't want it to fuzz.
Well, we're gonna need them.
For what?
Pull yourself together.
And take me to the boys.
Alright.
For Mickey.
But they aint gonna like you.
No one around here
respects you anymore.
Not since you walked.
Stay here,
I'll be back.
Fat boy!
Hello son.
How you doing?
Nice to see you.
How you feeling?
Feeling alright?
Just tell us Adam Shanko
put you up to this.
Cause we know.
And this would be all over.
When you get older.
People are always gonna describe
things to you by saying...
It's just like riding a bike.
So you got to learn.
They got Jade.
Yeah, don't worry.
He's good.
He won't talk.
Well, he better fucking not.
I got this,
I got this.
Jade...
This isn't a joke.
This is fucking real life.
Jade...
It's a girls name.
You'll be the biggest sissy
bitch on the wing.
What was your mother thinking?
Oi!
You promised you'd look after him.
- Yeah I will.
Well it doesn't look like it to me.
- It will only be a couple of..
Na na na.
My boy doing time is
not an option, yeah?
You don't tell a mother you're
going to look after her child...
And then speak:
It's only gonna be a bit of bird.
Yeah, but there's
nothing I can do.
Yes, there is.
No, there's not!
I've kept his nose clean for years now.
He'll be out in no time.
Oh, so while he's rotting in there,
you're on road yeah?
Listen...
I know where ever he was
that night, you where too.
Listen...
Don't make me call this geezer, yeah?
I'm telling you now,
don't make me call him.
Yeah, I'm being serious.
You'd better sort this out,
I want my child back.
I don't know why I have to go.
But they say they want me there.
I went to the wake.
I've made my peace,
that's it.
Listen, we need to talk.
Could you come around
my way and meet me?
I'm going away on business.
With Mike.
Yeah, I'm a bit worried
about something.
Why would I risk all this?
I'll see you then.
I just think he might
be planning something.
Yeah, well...
He won't be showing his face
around of red guards, would he?
Don't be so sure.
I'll run some checks.
I can't lose him now.
Not after everything
we've been through.
You've come a long way.
Yeah.
And I'm not going back.
You can't do that.
Ofcourse I can.
Check out the Plaza
down on Oxford Street.
Walk through to the main bit...
And look directly up.
It's an enormous pussy.
Staring straight at you.
A message from God.
Come here, let me show you something.
I'm gonna put some pussies
on either side. Yeah?
Like Brazilian foliage.
Nice and tidy, yeah?
Nice and tidy,
that's the one.
Bill?
Fuck.
Me.
Come here.
Are you alright, mate?
I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
You're looking stoosh.
What the fuck do you
bring him here for?
I like the idea.
I want to smash a couple
of those for a while now.
But not with you.
Are you fucking mad?
Ah c'mon, Bill.
We're stronger with you in it.
Always were.
Alright, get in the cage
with my boy.
Let's see if your arshole
is still intact.
You fucked of to the city
and left him for dead, so...
This is where we are.
All this trouble now,
we don't need him.
No, no, no...
We can do this.
And he fucking laughs around.
True.
Oi!
Mitch!
Come here.
How are you?
I'm alright.
Can we go now?
What are you gonna do
about the fucking ticket?
What you're gonna do...
Is you are gonna go on,
call the number on your ticket...
And you're gonna pay it
like a good boy, within 14 days...
Or it will double.
Next time you
park around here...
Read the fucking signs.
Open your mouth,
you lacking fucking prick.
Clownshoes.
Fancy a pint?
I was thinking about
going to Spain.
I've never been out of England before.
No, honoust, I've never done it.
Don't expect the beach,
we're gonna head for the hills.
Yeah, I'm up for that.
I'll make some calls.
What about your little brother?
Don't worry about him.
We're going.
Have you got any roads?
Yeah.
I was thinking, yeah,
if we do go to Spain...
Do you reckon we could
go to the new Cup?
I've heard about it.
Yeah, mate.
Yeah, we'll go both.
Yeah, do something with that.
I said: Do something with that.
I just remember I would
pick up my brother.
See you in a bit.
Oi, oi!
That's a 50 pound fine in here.
What?
Now listen...
Enjoy these,
these are smuggled...
All the way over from Cuba.
From my midget pal...
Guan.
Smuggled them.
Up his arse.
They taste like it, mate.
Yeah, well.
It's a long flight.
Let's go down there...
And knock them all out.
No.
Not this lad,
I mean they got teeth.
Seriously.
They're not silly.
Alright, we gotta trade careful.
I mean, there are only
a few that count.
If we got the head off...
The rest would scatter.
Guaranteed.
As long as we are straight,
I don't give a fuck about the other lot.
I'm straight.
You?
You know what this means.
Fuck that.
Don't be soft Mitch,
come on!
Trust me, you do not
want me at play.
Right, boy.
It's not everyday that
you win one of these.
We're gonna celebrate.
With a drinking game.
I'll put a song on.
And everytime he says 'house'...
You lot, will take a drink.
Everytime he says 'street'...
You lot drink.
Barman!
Do a shot now.
- Sure.
Are you having a
reunion without me?
Did I miss your email?
Or is it 'cause I'm a copper?
Mitch.
A word with you, please.
Yeah, 6 pm tomorrow.
Railerstreet.
Yeah, he is dealing with this one.
Cause I got shit with my brother.
Let's get it done, yeah?
Cool.
Who?
It's just a little pick me up.
Turn around.
Hello mate.
You're about to get fucked.
What the..?!
Oops.
What couldn't wait?
They knicked his righthand
man last night.
About time he did something.
We should make a move.
- Yeah.
Where are the others?
I don't know, I was
waiting for you.
He's gonna be out and
about soon, so...
Let's do it tonight.
Lovely.
So how do you think we knew
you were going to be there?
It's your job,
well done, boys.
Yeah, yeah.
But we're aren't sharp, are we?
Yeah...
We've must have had some help.
But who would want to help us?
Someone sold you out.
Your chart sheet is a joke, brother.
But, on the bright side...
We get to keep you here,
as long as we want.
Unless you give us Adam Shanko.
Well, think about it.
He goes inside...
You move up.
Can't give him up.
You might be just saving his life.
I hear...
There's a few of the old
faces back on the street.
That's it.
Bottom left pan corner.
Red door.
That one there?
Yeah.
He lives in his moms old house.
We're not going in.
I'm going on my own.
- No...
You fucking brought us here...
We'll go in together.
What the fucking hell
are you doing here?
You left your chain in my home...
I wanted to give it back.
Keep it.
And you stay the fuck
away from me.
Sports all over this gaff.
Don't worry about them,
I clocked them already.
I'll deal with them.
Look you lot leaving,
now back off.
I'll go alone...
And sort it out for another time.
Alright?
- No.
I'll go.
You're not the fucking
guvnor here.
Is this what's it all
about with you, Trent?
I thought this was
about Mickey?
You two, I can't have this here,
not now, alright?
Now fuck off,
I'll see you later.
Look, just...
I'll see you later, alright?
- I'm pregnant.
What?
Don't look at me like that.
We both know it's yours.
So, if you're still here tomorrow...
I'm gonna tell her.
Against the wall.
We need to talk.
I heard you're a man of
actions, not words.
Gun and blade.
Well, it looks like you got 1 gun.
Blade.
Sit the fuck down.
Do you mind if I smoke?
Yeah.
I do.
I'm glad I got away from all this.
I pitty you.
Can you put that sigaret out, please?
You don't even think about
the future, do you?
What happends when you're my age.
I'm hopeful thinking
you'll never get there.
Trust me.
I don't wanna get there.
You want my rep, right?
Then shoot me.
But know this...
Everyone around these flats
knows where I am.
You kill me here without
facing me on the street...
And you'll be known for what you are...
Scum.
But you'll be dead.
And me?
I then killed a legend.
That will be 2 in a week.
Fuck it.
Any last requests,
grandad?
Why the fuck are you
looking at me like?
That necklace.
It's a chain.
My mother bought it for me
from Malaysia, for my 18th.
You thought it was bullocks, isn't it?
Me and Stephen...
No fucking way.
She's your mom.
Don't fucking talk to me.
I got my family.
You're pointing that gun at it.
Get the fuck out of my house.
Put the gun down.
It's okay.
She fucking screwed you.
Then pull the trigger.
Do it!
Go on.
I'll let you live.
I really don't fucking wanna
know why I shouldn't.
Start again.
Like I did.
We don't all run away.
You should.
You got untill tomorrow.
You don't tell me what to do, yeah?
I can't sleep,
I had a bad dream.
Look, just go to next
door for me, yeah?
I'll come to you just
in a bit, alright?
I love you bro.
- Love you too.
Don't be a fucking prick.
Don't.
I got lucky.
I got a second chance.
Don't be stupid and
pass this one up, kid.
You're my birth and
I will let you live.
But if you're here tomorrow...
Yeah then what?
Then I'll fucking kill you.
Mitch Raymond use to run
a firm called The Guvnors.
Yeah.
You know them well.
Too fucking well.
You'll probably purview your
mates on a drip.
It would definitely do Shanko.
Unless you give me,
what I want.
I am gonna start playing and
watch your fucking family burn.
I will make sure not a single copper
from this station steps in to help.
I will take him around your
fucking house.
I would introduce him to
your fucking family.
Nah.
I won't give you Shanko.
I don't want Shanko.
What the fuck do you want then?
I want the gun.
How's that gonna help?
It's gonna make me look good.
Impossible.
When I've got it,
it won't be used.
There is no gun.
We don't have one.
You little fucking pig.
Outside.
- Nah leave it, Bill.
What the fuck are you
always defending him for?
He fucking mocked us
off our on turf.
It's a bit more complicated then that.
Nah, nah, it's very uncomplicated.
He walks out on us.
He cost Charly his life.
I shouldn't have let it go.
But I did.
And now he wants to come and
disrespect us, on our own manner.
And I'm thinking...
I'm having none of that.
He's my son.
The kid.
I've just found out.
I'm probably gonna have
to batter this lad tomorrow.
It's not ideal, but I don't
a fucking choise.
I was thinking that
the few of us...
Sit down and have a
quiet drink together.
I feel like a donkeys arshole.
See you...
You're a right shit stirrer.
All afternoon he's have
me go on about you.
All fucking afternoon.
You were lucky...
Cause if I would've pinged you...
You would've gone over like
an old granny of a sheet of ice.
I'll drink to that.
Cheers.
I got set up.
Which means one
of you fuckers...
Is a grass.
Someone needs to talk.
See this boys...
This is all I've got.
I ain't got no family.
I ain't got no mom.
I ain't got no fucking dad.
You boys...
You boys is all I've got.
So when someone breaks my trust.
It fucking hurts, you know?
Woods, step forward.
Talk to me, Woods.
Ain't no grass here.
Is that right?
Yeah, not here.
You need to find one, Woods.
Today...
Woods...
Is being promoted.
With Trey inside, I need a
new guy, and Woods...
You're my new guy.
Your first assignment...
Is to cut one of these
fuckers for being a grass.
I don't care who it is...
Someone gets cut.
Now!
Hold him.
I said nothing.
Hold him!
I said nothing!
Tomorrow...
We go into war.
There's gonna be loads of them.
That's what I need you to do...
Is round up every little
fucking rat on this estate
To come fight, alright?
Be ready.
Where's Mitch?
I think he's lost his head.
He was saying some weird
shit in the pub last night.
Some bird came in and
he just left in a hurry.
What do you mean?
Like he said; He lost
his fucking nut.
Ain't no fucking surprise there, is it?
Anyway, fuck him.
You stay in here, alright?
We need to focus.
Let me talk to him.
Trent.
What?
Alright, so what are
we gonna do now?
We'll be fine.
We got plenty here.
Mitch!
Mitch?!
Here's Malor.
- Were is he?
Hello Ange.
I'm going to Fredcast to find him.
Angie, he's fine.
I've seen him.
He's coming home.
Are you with him?
Not right now, no.
But I'm meeting him.
He's not on the estate.
He's fine. He'll be home later.
Where is he?
Go home, wait.
I'll bring him to you, trust me.
Yeah, this is me, it's Malor...
I need an ambulance.
A gunshot injury of
urgent medical attention.
I have the suspect
in custody.
I've secured the gun.
Just get an ambulance here, will you?
Big tough guy like you...
You'll be alright.
You need a bit pressure on it.
Oi, I made a promise to Angie
I would take you home, alright?
So we get you patched up...
And I'm gonna get you back.
You're going home soon!
I hope and pray,
that you make the right decision...
And walk away from this fight.
From this life...
But even as I write this letter
I know that you won't...
Because it's who we are.
For me...
To find the strenght and
courage to walk away...
It took finding someone
I couldn't affort to lose.
Someone who loved me for who I am.
And now...
Because of a mistake I made
20 years ago...
I find myself right back
where I started.
Funny...
How faith never forgets.
One of us won't
be going home tomorrow.
You and I both know that.
But I guess there comes
a point in every mans life...
When he has to stop pretending
he's something he's not.
I'll get my revenge for Mickey.
He was a good man.
You could've learned a lot from him...
He would've told you to walk...
Cause it's the bravest thing
you could do.
No one ever drowned by
getting in water, son.
You'll only drown if you stay in it.